A Guide to the Louis Arthur Johnson Papers, ca. 1930-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Papers of the Assistant Secretary of War, 1936 (1937-1940)1941
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence
    - Correspondence-Lookabill, L. E. ca. 1939 Jan.-1940 April (Box 17)
    - Correspondence-Lyon, Norman "Pat" ca. 1938 Jan.-1939 March (Box 17)
    - Correspondence-General (La) 1937-1940 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence-General (Le-Ly), 4 folders 1937-1940 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence-McFarland, Earl (Lt. Col., Ordnance Dept.) 1932 Jan.-1936 Jan. (Box 18)
    - Correspondence-McGrail, Edward 1937 Sept.-1940 June (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-McKay, Osborne E. ca. 1937 July-1939 Aug. (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-McKee, Mark T. ca. 1937 Dec.-1940 June (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-McKenzie, Charles ca. 1937 Sept.-1939 April (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-MacKenzie, Vic 1940 April-May (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-McManaway, J. C. 1937 July-1940 July (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-McNutt, Paul V. ca. 1937 Sept.-1940 March (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Mallison, Hon. Sam T. ca. 1937 Nov.-1939 Aug. (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Manly, Basil 1938 June-1940 April (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Martigny, Francois de. 1937 Sept.-1939 Dec. (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Meyer, Eugene 1938 Nov.-1939 Sept. (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Miller, Earl ca. 1937 Dec.-1939 Sept. (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Miller, Harlan ca. 1939 May-1940 June (Box 19)
    - Correspondence--Miller, Watson B. ca. 1937 July-1939 Oct. (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Minton, Sherman ca. 1938 June-1939 Feb. (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Mitchell, Harry L. ca. 1937 July-1940 June (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Moore, George, M. 1939 Jan.-1940 June (Box 19)
    - Correspondence-Morris, Bernard C. ca. 1938 Nov.-1940 Jan. (Box 20)
    - Correspondence-Morris, Hon. James W. ca. 1938 Jan.-1939 May (Box 20)
    - Correspondence-General (McA-Map), 5 folders 1937-1940 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence-General (Mar-Mowles), 4 folders 1937-1940 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence-General (Mu-My) 1937-1940 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence-Neely, M. M. ca. 1937 Sept.-1940 May (Box 22)
    - Correspondence-Nesbitt, Gen. Carl 1937 Aug.-1938 Jan. (Box 22)
    - Correspondence-General (Na-Nu), 2 folders 1937-1940 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence-O'Connor, Basil ca. 1939 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence-O'Connor, J. F. T. ca. 1937 Jan.-1939 March (Box 22)
    - Correspondence-Ogden, Herschel ca. 1938 Dec.-1939 Jan. (Box 22)
    - Correspondence-General (Oa-Ou) 1937-1940 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence-Parks, Major John N. 1937 Nov.-1938 Oct. (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-Pershing, Gen. John J. ca. 1938 March-1939 April (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-Persons, W. Frank ca. 1937 Dec. (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-Philips, Harold K. ca. 1937 July-1940 May (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-Pollard, Robert ca. 1937 Oct.-1940 Jan. (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-Pollitz, Colonel Walter S. ca. 1938 Sept.-1940 May (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-Porter, Hon. H. Hobart 1937 Nov.-1940 May (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-Pownall, Hetz ca. 1937 Aug.-1939 Jan. (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-General (Pa) 1937-1940 (Box 23)
    - Correspondence-General (Pe-Py), 4 folders 1937-1940 (Box 24)
    - Correspondence-Quinn, Hon. John R. ca. 1937 Aug.-1940 March (Box 24)
    - Correspondence-General (Q) 1937-1940 (Box 24)
    - Correspondence-Ramsay, Hon. D. H. ca. 1938 Aug.-1939 Jan. (Box 24)
    - Correspondence-Randerson, J. Howard ca. 1937 July-1940 July (Box 24)
    - Correspondence-Randolph, J. H. 1937 Jan.-1940 April (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Randolph, Hon. Jennings 1937 July-1940 Jan. (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Redden, Harold P. ca. 1938 March-1940 Feb. (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Reynolds, S. W. ca. 1937 May-1940 May (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Reynolds, W. D. ca. 1937 Aug.-Sept. (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Rhawn, H. G. 1937 July-1940 June (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Robinson, Claude ca. 1937 Sept.-1940 May (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Robinson, Joseph W. 1938 Oct.-1940 June (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Rolland, Eugene ca. 1938 Jan.-1940 Jan. (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Ross, Philip, L., Jr. ca. 1938 June-1940 May (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Rushton, Col. Marion ca. 1938 Nov.-1940 May (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-Ryan, Oswald ca. 1937 Aug.-1940 May (Box 25)
    - Correspondence-General (Ra-Ror), including memoranda to the President, FDR, 6 folders 1937-1940 (Box 26)
    - Correspondence-General (Ros-Ry), 2 folders 1937-1940 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Scott, Major Ralph Cook 1938 June-1940 April (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Shaver, Hon. Clem ca. 1937 Aug.-1938 Dec. (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Shingleton, Col. P. D. 1937 Aug.-1940 July (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Shoop, Hon. Max 1937 Oct.-1940 May (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Silcox, Helen ca. 1937 Oct.-1939 June (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Siminoff, Capt. Tony 1939 Feb.-1940 April (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Simpson, Burr, H., Commissioner, W. Va. 1937 July-1940 March (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Simpson, Hon. Clarence M. 1938 Dec.-1939 Sept. (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Smith, C. E. 1938 Jan.-1939 Sept. (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Smith, C. R. ca. 1938 March-1940 June (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Smith, Charles Brooks ca. 1939 Nov.-1940 May (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Smith, Claude 1937 Sept.-1940 May (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Snedeker, Albert ca. 1938 June-1939 Nov. (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Snoberger, R. E. ca. 1938 Nov.-1940 Feb. (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Spear, Hon Nathaniel, J 1937 Oct.-1940 June (Box 27)
    - Correspondence-Spurr, A. C. 1937 July-1940 July (Box 28)
    - Correspondence-Starling, Howard M. 1938 Feb.-1939 Oct. (Box 28)
    - Correspondence-Stern, Samuel ca. 1938 Sept.-1939 June (Box 28)
    - Correspondence-Stettinius, Edward R., Jr.; Correspondence and copies of Stettinius Sr's War Correspondence 1918 March-1921 Jan., 1938 April-1940 May (Box 28)
    - Correspondence-Strosnider, Hon. Homer ca. 1937 Oct.-1940 May (Box 28)
    - Correspondence-Sullivan, John L. ca. 1938 Oct.-1939 Dec. (Box 28)
    - Correspondence-Swearingen, W. Dean 1937 July-1940 June (Box 28)
    - Correspondence-General (Sa-Sha), 3 folders 1937-1940 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence-General (She-Sta), 5 folders 1937-1940 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence-General (Ste-Sz), 3 folders 1937-1940 (Box 30)
    - Correspondence-Tabler, Ray ca. 1937 Aug.-1938 March (Box 30)
    - Correspondence-Thompson, E. S. ca. 1937 Sept.-1940 April (Box 30)
    - Correspondence-Thurmond, Hon. Walter ca. 1937 Aug.-1939 Jan. (Box 30)
    - Correspondence-Tim, Louis B. ca. 1938 May-1940 June (Box 30)
    - Correspondence-Toulmin, Col. H. A. Jr. ca. 1937 July-1940 July (Box 30)
    - Correspondence-Treadwell, Joseph A. ca. 1937 Dec.-1940 Feb. (Box 30)
    - Correspondence-General (Ta-Th) 1937-1940 (Box 30)
    - Correspondence-General (Ti-V), 3 folders 1937-1940 (Box 31)
    - Correspondence-Witherell, Walter B. 1939-1940 (Box 31)
    - Correspondence-General (Wa-Wh), 3 folders 1937-1940 (Box 31)
    - Correspondence-General (Wic-Z), 6 folders 1937-1940 (Box 32)
  - Subseries B, Case Files, 1937-1940
    - Aeronautics-Correspondence re: Civil Aeronautics Authority 1938 May-1940 April (Box 33)
    - Aeronautics-Correspondence with Harilee Branch, Vice Chairman, Civil Aeronautics Authority 1937 Dec.-1939 Nov. (Box 33)
    - Aids to Secretary of War, Civilian and Military-Correspondence 1937 May-Aug. (Box 33)
    - Air Power, Comparison of Major Nations-Correspondence and Papers 1938 Dec.-1939 Jan. (Box 33)
    - Aircraft-Correspondence and Papers re: Supplemental Estimate of Funds for Procurement of Airplanes 1939 Jan. (Box 33)
    - Aircraft-Breakdown of cost of 1,000 Army Airplanes 1938 Oct. (Box 33)
    - Aircraft-Outline Policy of the War and Navy Depts. For export and domestic sale of aircraft and aircraft equipment 1939 Sept.-Oct. (Box 33)
    - Aircraft-Clippings 1940 March 25-27 (Box 33)
    - Aircraft-Newspaper Clippings 1940 March-April (Box 34)
    - Aircraft-Correspondence and Papers 1938 Sept.-Nov. (Box 34)
    - Aircraft Expansion-Correspondence and Papers 1938 Dec.-1940 June (Box 34)
    - Aircraft Expansion Conference-Correspondence and Papers 1938 Oct.-Dec. (Box 34)
    - Aircraft Expansion Conference, 1939 July 10-Correspondence and Proceedings 1939 June-July (Box 34)
    - Aircraft Expansion-Memoranda to Johnson and Papers 1938 Oct. (Box 34)
    - Aircraft Expansion-Press Releases 1938 Nov. 23 (Box 34)
    - Aircraft Expansion, Navy-Correspondence 1938 Oct.-1939 Sept. (Box 35)
    - Aircraft Expansion, Requirements and Resources-Correspondence and Papers 1938 Oct.-Nov. (Box 35)
    - Aircraft, Foreign Sale of-Newspaper Clippings, 2 folders 1940 Feb. 4-March 24 (Box 35)
    - Aircraft, Procurement Act of 1939-Papers 1939 Jan.-March (Box 35)
    - Airplanes, Sale of to Allies-Newspaper Clippings 1940 April-May (Box 35)
    - Alaska-Correspondence 1938 Aug.-1940 June (Box 35)
    - Allison Engineering Co. Trip-Newspaper Clippings 1939 Dec. (Box 36)
    - American Bar Association-Correspondence re: Johnson's Membership on Marine and Inland Marine Insurance Law Committee 1939 Sept.-Nov. (Box 36)
    - American Legion-Correspondence 1937 July-1938 Feb. (Box 36)
    - American Legion-Correspondence and Papers re: Voiture Nationale La Societé Des 40 Hommes et 8 Chevaux 1937 Aug.-1940 May (Box 36)
    - American Legion Convention, Los Angeles-Log of calls to Johnson's Headquarters 1938 Sept. 17-21 (Box 36)
    - American Legion Convention, 1939-Correspondence 1939 April-Oct. (Box 36)
    - American Legion Convention, 1939 Correspondence re: Department Commander's Dinner 1938 Oct.-1939 Dec. (Box 36)
    - American Legion Convention, 1939-Johnson's Schedule and Correspondence, includes an index 1939 ca. Jan.-ca. Nov. (Box 36)
    - American Legion, Department of West Va.-Correspondent and Papers 1937 July-1940 ca. June (Box 36)
    - American Legion, District of Columbia Department Convention-Correspondence 1940 July-Aug. (Box 36)
    - American Legion, Federation Interalliee Des Anciens Combattants-Correspondence 1937 Aug.-1940 June (Box 36)
    - American Legion, National Headquarters-Correspondence and Papers 1937 July-1940 July (Box 37)
    - American Legion, National Headquarters-Correspondence with E. O. Marquette 1937 Jan.-1940 June (Box 37)
    - American Legion, Pershing Hall (Paris) Committee-Correspondence and Proceedings 1937 July-Aug. (Box 37)
    - American Legion, Roy E. Parrish Post - Correspondence 1937 Aug.-1939 Aug. (Box 37)
    - American Legion State-Wide Meeting, Wisconsin-Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1939 Dec.-1940 March (Box 37)
    - Americanization Day, Pittsburgh-Correspondence re: Johnson's Speech 1939 Dec.-1940 May (Box 37)
    - Annual Reports by Assistant Secretary of War 1937-1939 (Box 37)
    - Annual Report of Assistant Secretary of War-Newspaper Clippings 1940 Jan. (Box 37)
    - Appointments with Johnson-Correspondence and Memoranda, 2 folders 1937 July-1938 April (Box 38)
    - Appointments, 3 folders 1938 April-Dec. (Box 38)
    - Appointments, 5 folders 1938 Dec.-1939 Nov. (Box 39)
    - Appointments, 5 folders 1939 Nov.-1940 May (Box 40)
    - Appointments, 5 folders 1940 May-July (Box 41)
    - Apprentice Training in Industry-Correspondence and News Release 1939 Feb.-Oct. (Box 42)
    - Apprentice Training of Mechanics-Proposed Program 1939 March (Box 42)
    - Army-Weekly Summaries of Activities 1939 July 27-1940 July 19 (Box 42)
    - Army Air Corp-Supplemental Budget, 1940, Correspondence and Papers 1939 Jan. (Box 42)
    - Army Day Celebration, New York, April 6, 1940-Correspondence, Speech by Johnson, Photographs 1940 Feb.-April (Box 42)
    - Army Industrial College-Correspondence 1938 March-May (Box 42)
    - Army and Navy Club-Correspondence and Printed Material 1939 Aug.-1940 Jan. (Box 42)
    - Army-Navy Country Club-Correspondence and Printed Material 1937 July-1940 April (Box 42)
    - Army-Navy Football Game-Requests to Johnson for tickets 1937 Oct.-Nov. (Box 42)
    - Army-Navy Football 1937 Oct.-Nov. (Box 42)
    - Army-Navy Football 1937 Oct.-Nov. (Box 43)
    - Army-Navy Football Game-Requests to Johnson for tickets 1938 Oct.-Nov. (Box 43)
    - Army-Navy Football, 3 folders 1938 Oct.-Nov. (Box 43)
    - Army-Navy Football 1939 Oct.-Nov. (Box 44)
    - Army-Navy Football Game-Requests to Johnson for tickets 1939 Sept.-Dec. (Box 44)
    - Army and Navy Munitions Board-Correspondence and Papers 1939 Aug.-1940 May (Box 44)
    - Articles in Newspapers and Periodicals and Related Correspondence 1937 Aug.-1938 June (Box 44)
    - Articles-Correspondence, 4 folders 1938 Feb.-1939 Jan. (Box 45)
    - Articles-Correspondence, 5 folders 1939 Sept.-1940 July (Box 46)
    - Associated General Contractors of America-Correspondence re: Johnson's Speech at Annual Convention, and papers 1939 Dec.-1940 (Box 47)
    - Association of American Railroads - Correspondence and Papers re: Johnson's Speech at Dedication of Services of American Railroads in WWI, 2 folders 1940 March-July (Box 47)
    - Aviation-Correspondence and Papers re: Legislation to create Civil Aeronautics Board, 2 folders 1937 Sept.-1938 Feb. (Box 47)
    - Aviation, Pilot Training Program-Correspondence and Proposal for Program 1938 Nov.-Dec. (Box 48)
    - Aviation-Related Topics-Correspondence and Papers 1935, 1936 (1937 July-Nov.) (Box 48)
    - Aviation-Related Topics-Correspondence and Papers, 3 folders 1937 Nov.-1938 Oct. (Box 48)
    - Aviation-Related Topics-Correspondence and Papers, 2 folders 1938 Oct.-1940 July (Box 49)
    - Aviation, Vocational Training in - Correspondence and Papers 1938 Dec. 13-17 (Box 49)
    - Aviation - Memo from Col. B. Q. Jones re: Current situation of Military, Aviation 1938 Oct. 13 (Box 49)
    - Aviation - Committee on Civil Aviation Legislation - Minutes of meetings 1937 Sept. 30-Nov. 5 (Box 49)
    - Aviation - Press Releases 1938-1940 (Box 49)
    - Barlow Bomb - Newspaper Clippings 1940 March (Box 49)
    - Battle of New Orleans Celebration - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1939 Dec.-1940 Jan. (Box 49)
    - B'nai B'rith Celebration, New York - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1940 Jan.-March (Box 50)
    - Booneville Dam-Correspondence and Papers and Photographs 1935 (1938 Jan.-1939 March) (Box 50)
    - Boston City Club-Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1939 Oct.-1940 Feb. (Box 50)
    - Budget Estimates of Military - Correspondence and Documents, including Congressional Military Appropriation Bills 1939 Nov.-1940 July (Box 50)
    - Burning Tree Club - Correspondence and Papers 1937 Aug.-1940 Jan. (Box 50)
    - Chemical Warfare Service - Correspondence and Memoranda 1939 Sept.-1940 May (Box 50)
    - Civil Aeronautics Authority - Memoranda 1938 June-1940 May (Box 50)
    - Civilian Conservation Corps - Memoranda by Col. Crain 1933 Aug.-1934 Jan. (Box 50)
    - Civilian Conservation Corps - Correspondence 1937 Nov.-1939 May (Box 51)
    - Civilian Conservation Corp, West Virginia - Correspondence and Memoranda 1937 Nov.-1938 March (Box 51)
    - Clarksburg, W. Va. Airport - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address on opening of Airport 1940 May - June (Box 51)
    - Clarksburg, W. Va. Airport - Correspondence re: Construction 1937 Aug.-1938 April (Box 51)
    - Clarksburg, W. Va. Chamber of Commerce-Correspondence and Papers re: Airport 1937 April-1940 Jan. (Box 51)
    - Clarksburg, W. Va. Chamber of Commerce-Correspondence and Papers 1940 Feb.-July (Box 51)
    - Clarksburg, W. Va., Junior Chamber of Commerce - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1940 April-May (Box 51)
    - Commission in the Army-Correspondence 1937 July-1940 July (Box 51)
    - Conference held by Johnson-Correspondence and Memoranda 1937 June-1940 May (Box 51)
    - Congratulations to Johnson re: Appointment as Assistant Secretary of War, A-B. 1937 June-July (Box 51)
    - Congratulations to Johnson re: Appointment as Assistant Secretary of War, C-M, 5 folders 1937 June-July (Box 52)
    - Congratulations to Johnson re: Appointment as Assistant Secretary of War, O-Z, 3 folders 1937 June-July (Box 53)
    - Contributions and Dues of Johnson-Correspondence 1937 Oct.-1940 July (Box 53)
    - Cooperative Committee - Correspondence between Johnson and Charles Estes, Chairman 1937 Aug.-Dec. (Box 53)
    - Current Procurement-Correspondence and Memoranda 1938 Jan.-1940 June (Box 53)
    - Delta Chi Fraternity-Correspondence 1939 Nov. 20, 21 (Box 54)
    - Democratic National Committee - Correspondence 1937 Sept. 1940 Jan. (Box 54)
    - Democratic National Committee - Correspondence and Memoranda communicated to Ambrose O'Connell, Executive Assistant, Democrat National Committee 1937 Dec.-1939 June (Box 54)
    - Democratic National Convention, Chicago, 1940-Telegrams re: Johnson's Candidacy for Vice-President, Correspondence and list of Delegates 1940 July (Box 54)
    - Earle Thompson Dinner-Correspondence re: Johnson's attendance 1940 Jan.-March (Box 54)
    - Education Order to Industry-Correspondence and Papers 1937 Nov.-1940 June (Box 54)
    - Educational Orders-Newspaper Clippings 1940 March-May (Box 54)
    - Election Congratulations, from Johnson to Congressmen, A-F1938 Nov. (Box 54)
    - Election Congratulations, G-Z1938 Nov.-Dec. (Box 55)
    - Emergency Measures by War Department in event of War in Europe 1939 Aug.-Sept. (Box 55)
    - Employment, Requests for Aid in Securing, 2 folders 1937 June-Nov. (Box 55)
    - Employment, 6 folders 1937 Nov.-1940 April (Box 56)
    - Employment, 6 folders 1937 Aug.-1940 June (Box 57)
    - Employment, 5 folders 1938 Dec.-1939 Nov. (Box 58)
    - Employment, 4 folders 1939 Oct.-1940 July (Box 59)
    - Employment Service of W. Va., 2 folders 1937 July-1940 May (Box 59)
    - Engineering Society of Western Pennsylvania - Correspondence re: Johnson's Speech 1939 March-1940 April (Box 60)
    - Enlisted Men, Correspondence re: 1937 Aug.-1940 June (Box 60)
    - Executive Council Reports to Secretary of War 1933 (Box 60)
    - Fairchild's Dinner celebrating opening of American League Baseball Season - Correspondence re: Johnson's Attendance 1940 Feb.-April (Box 60)
    - Federal Security Agency-Correspondence 1939 May-Sept. (Box 60)
    - Flood Control-Correspondence and Papers 1937 Aug.-1940 Jan. (Box 60)
    - Flood Control-Correspondence and Printed Material re: New England Council 1937 Aug.-Nov. (Box 60)
    - Flood Control, Grafton Dam - Correspondence 1937 Aug.-1938 Sept. (Box 60)
    - Flood Control, Grafton Dam and Tygart River Reservoir - Correspondence re: Dedication 1937 Aug.-1939 Nov. (Box 60)
    - Flood Control - Printed Material 1937-1938 (Box 61)
    - Fuel Engineering Conference - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1940 May-July (Box 61)
    - Governorship of West Virginia for Johnson-Newspaper Clippings 1940 March-April (Box 61)
    - Harvard Business School - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1940 April-June (Box 61)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar - Addresses 1938 Nov.-1940 June (Box 61)
    - 1939 House of Representatives - Bill #3518 (Box 61)
    - Industrial Mobilization - Correspondence and Papers re: Procurement Planning 1938 Feb.-1940 May (Box 61)
    - Industrial Mobilization Plan - Printed Material 1939 (Box 61)
    - Industrial Mobilization Plan - Cherne Book - Newspaper Clippings 1939 Sept.-1940 May (Box 61)
    - Informal Memoranda and Notes re: Contracts, etc. ca. 1931 Sept.-1934 July (Box 62)
    - Information - Log of Requests for information from War Department, 3 folders 1939 Sept. 18-1940 Feb. 17 (Box 62)
    - Institute of Food Technologists - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1940 May-July (Box 62)
    - Intercollegiate Flying Association - Correspondence 1938 Oct. 28-31 (Box 62)
    - Introductions Abroad by Johnson, A-Z, 2 folders ca. 1937-ca.1940 (Box 62)
    - Inventions related to military - Correspondence and Documents 1938 July-1940 July (Box 62)
    - Invitations accepted by Johnson, 4 folders 1937 June-Nov. (Box 63)
    - Invitations accepted by Johnson, 5 folders 1937 Nov.-1939 June (Box 64)
    - Invitations accepted by Johnson, 5 folders 1939 Feb.-1940 July (Box 65)
    - Invitations to Johnson - Response: Indefinite 1939-1940 (Box 65)
    - Jackson Day Dinner, Atlanta, Ga., Jan. 8, 1940 - Correspondence re: Johnson's Speech, Speech Guest List 1939 Dec.-1940 May (Box 66)
    - Jackson Day Dinner, Atlanta, Ga.-Newspaper Clippings ca. 1940 Jan. (Box 66)
    - Johnson, Louis - Sketch of his life to 1940 1940 April 20 (Box 66)
    - Johnson's Membership on Boards, Committees, Clubs - Correspondence ca. 1937 July-1940 June (Box 66)
    - Johnson's reply to Hoover - Newspaper Clippings 1940 May - June (Box 66)
    - Johnson's Speech at New Orleans Celebration - Newspaper Clippings 1940 Jan. (Box 66)
    - Kentucky Derby - Correspondence re: Johnson's Attendance 1939 May-1940 May (Box 66)
    - Kenyon College - Correspondence and Papers re: Johnson's Honorary Law Degree 1940 May-June (Box 66)
    - Legal Claims - Correspondence and Memoranda 1937 Sept.-1938 Aug. (Box 67)
    - Legislation-Correspondence and Papers 1937 July-1940 June (Box 67)
    - Lilly Family Reunion - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address, Program of Reunion 1939 June-Aug. (Box 67)
    - May, Congressman Andrew J., Conflict of Interest - Newspaper Clippings 1940 Jan. (Box 67)
    - Mechanics' Training - Correspondence and Memoranda 1938 July-1940 June (Box 67)
    - Mechanization of Army - Correspondence between Johnson and H. A. Toulmin and Memoranda 1938 March-June (Box 67)
    - Memoranda 1937 June - 1940 May (Box 67)
    - Memoranda to Staff 1939 Jan. - 1940 July (Box 68)
    - Memorandum to Johnson re: Members of Press to attend Conference 1937 July 7 (Box 68)
    - Metropolitan Club-Correspondence re: Johnson's Membership 1937 Oct.-1940 April (Box 68)
    - Military Academies-Correspondence re: Appointments to Academies, 2 folders 1937 July-1939 Aug. (Box 69)
    - Military Officers - Correspondence, 3 folders 1937 Dec.-1940 Feb. (Box 69)
    - Military Officers - Correspondence, 2 folders 1939 Feb.-1940 July (Box 69)
    - Monongahela West Penn Public Service Co. - Correspondence 1937 Aug. 19-27 (Box 69)
    - Mountain State Forest Festival, W. Va. - Correspondence 1937 Sept.-Oct. (Box 69)
    - Munitions Preparedness under Protective Mobilization Plan - Correspondence and Papers 1938 March-1940 Feb. (Box 69)
    - Munitions Purchases by Foreign Countries - Newspaper Clippings 1939 Nov.-1940 April (Box 69)
    - Munitions, Types and quantities of - Memoranda 1939 Sept.-Oct. (Box 69)
    - National Association of Manufacturers - Correspondence re: Johnson's Speech at Dinner and Memoranda 1940 Jan.-March (Box 69)
    - National Association of Purchasing Agents Convention, Cincinnati, June 4, 1940 - Correspondence and Papers, including speech by Johnson 1940 March-July (Box 69)
    - National Board of Fire Underwriters - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1940 April-June (Box 69)
    - National Board of Fire Underwriters - Correspondence re: Johnson's Address 1940 May-July (Box 70)
    - National Board of Fire Underwriters - Correspondence to Members Thanking them for Invitations to speak at Annual Meeting 1940 May-June (Box 70)
    - National Board of Fire Underwriters - Clippings re: Johnson's Address 1940 May-June (Box 70)
    - National Defense - Correspondence and Address of President Roosevelt to Congress 1937 Sept.-ca. 1940 July (Box 70)
    - National Defense - Correspondence and Papers re: Supply Preparedness 1940 May-July (Box 70)
    - National Defense - Correspondence by Johnson in Response to Offers of Service 1940 May-July (Box 70)
    - National Defense - Newspaper Clippings 1940 Jan.-May (Box 70)
    - National Defense, Advisory Commission to Council of - Correspondence and Papers 1940 June-July (Box 70)